knoll.com 2014-11-22

# Knoll

  * print

This Privacy Policy explains Knoll®'s policy regarding the privacy of information supplied by users or collected by us from users of this Knoll Web Site. Because we want to build users trust and confidence in this web site, we want to disclose our privacy practices.

### Modifications

Since this policy may change over time as we modify or expand our services, we suggest that you check back from time to time in order to understand how we treat your information.

### What Personally Identifiable Information Is Collected

This web site's various registration forms require users to give us contact information (such as name, address and email address). Certain other information, such as demographic information and responses to market surveys may be collected by us during the registration process. In addition, when purchasing products, programs and services through this web site, we will collect financial information, such as credit card information. Not all information is required to be provided (required items will be clearly noted), but if you should choose to withhold any requested information, you may not be eligible to participate in or receive full benefit from all products, programs and services on the web site.

We also use your internet protocol ("IP") address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

### How Information Is Used And With Whom It Is Shared

We use your personally identifiable information to enhance this web site and to personalize your experience. We use customer contact information from various registration forms to send the user information about our products and services and promotional material from some of our partners and affiliates. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with our affiliated companies and authorized third-party service providers.

We also may run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some other companies with whom we do business. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with our affiliated companies and authorized third-party service providers.

Financial information that is collected from our users may be used to check a user’s qualifications for registration and bill the user for products and services. We will not sell your financial information to third parties. This web site also supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

We may also collect and report to third parties (such as affiliates, content and service providers and advertisers) aggregated information from this web site. For example, we may aggregate and report to third parties that X people purchased a particular product during a month, or that Y% of visitors to this web site are between the ages 25-34.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are an industry standard practice of placing a file or identifying "marker" on a user's computer for identification and personalization purposes. Our site may use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and your identity when you use our site. Our cookies do not have the capability of "stealing" information from your hard drive. You are not required to accept cookies. However, certain functionality of this web site may not work properly (if at all) if you reject cookies.

### Third Parties

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such web sites. Third parties may collect information about you when you view and/or click on their advertising, and we do not control the collection of this information.

### Security

We use certain efforts to secure our web site such as firewalls and authentication protection. We will periodically review our security policies and implement changes from time to time. However, we cannot and do not guarantee complete security, as it does not exist on the Internet.

### Children

You must be 18 years or older to use this web site, and therefore we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under age 18. If you are under age 18, please ask your parent before sending any information to our site or anyone else online. Have your parent contact us as indicated below in order to provide us with prior written consent. We will not intentionally use personal information from or send marketing communications to children under age 13 without prior parental consent.

### Legally Required Disclosures

We may be required, by applicable law, subpoena, court order or other legal process to disclose your personally identifiable information, and it is our policy to comply with any such requirements.

### Contacting Knoll

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us:

Knoll, Inc.  
1235 Water Street  
East Greenville, PA 18041  
800 343-5665
